https://www.melfredborzall.com/privacy-policy/

Shop by DRILL RIG
D6x6 D7x11 D7x11A D7x11A S2 D8x12 D9x13 D9x13 S2 D9x13 S3 D10x15 D10x15 S3 D16x20 D16x20 S2 D18x22 D20x22 S2 D20x22 S3 D23x30 S3 D24x26 D24x33 D24x40 D24x40A D24x40 S2 D24x40 S3 D33x44 D36x50 D36x50 S3 D36x50 DR S2 D40x40 D40x55 D40x55 S3 D40x55 DR S3 D50x100 D60x90 D60x90 S3 D80x100 D80x120 D80x100 S2 D100x120 D100x120 S2 D100x140 D100x140 S3 D220x300 D220x300 S3 JT5 JT9 JT10 JT20 JT20XP JT25 JT30 JT30 AT JT40 JT40 AT JT60 JT60 AT JT100 JT100 M1 JT100 AT JT520 JT920 JT920L JT921 JT922 JT1220 M1 JT1720 JT1720 M1 JT2720 JT2020 JT2720 M1 JT2720 AT JT3020 JT3020 AT JT4020 JT4020 M1 JT4020 AT JT7020 JT7020 M1 JT8020 JT8020 M1 DD4 DD5 DD6 DD8 DD10 DD65 DD220T DD1215 DD1416 DD2024 DD2226 DD3238 DD4045 DD4050 DD9014 4X
Shop by Part #
Shop by Ground Condition
DIRT
SHALE
GRAVEL
SAND
SANDSTONE
COBBLES
Tool Talk Videos & Media
Download Catalog (PDF)
Help & Contact
Toll-Free 800.558.7500
International 805.739.0118
Monday - Friday 8 - 5 PST
Contact Us
Shipping
Warranty
Returns
Account Find a DistributorMy Borzall
My Cart
Find a Distributor
Choose Your Location:Domestic (US) International
Privacy Policy
Your Privacy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for MelfredBorzall.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site (the “Personal Data”). We only have access to/collect Personal Data that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this Personal Data to anyone.
We will use your Personal Data to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your Personal Data with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
The Following Applies to Individuals Whose Personal Data Falls Under the Jurisdictions Subject to the E.U.’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR):
Melfred Borzall, Inc. is the Data Controller for your Personal Data. Your consent to our use of the Personal Data provides Melfred Borzall with a lawful basis for such use. We will retain the Personal Data indefinitely unless you instruct us to delete it or we inform you otherwise. If you feel that there is a problem with how the Personal Data has been handled, you have the right to register a complaint with a supervisory authority.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Do-Not-Track Signals
Our website includes third-party applications that track visitors. The following applications do not respond to Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) requests. Clicking on the links will bring up their privacy policies. AddThis.com, AdRoll.com, LiveChatInc.com, Adnxs.com, Facebook.com, and YouTube.com. Those applications that do respond to DNT do not drop cookies into visitors’ browsers.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately info@melfredborzall.com.
